本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
噢  不  梅宝  我有点不舒服
Oh, no Mabel. I... I don't feel so good!
我
I...
噢  斯坦叔公  你给我们吃了什么
Ohh! Grunkle Stan, what did you feed us?
-吐啊  -小鬼们  别闹了
-Barfy! -Guys, stop!
刚才发生了很糟糕的事情
Something terrible just happened!
-撒金子啦  -闹够了  行了
-Comedy gold! -All right, all right!
派对用品现在禁用了
Party supplies are now off-limits.
派恩斯先生  这是谁的生日来着
Mr. Pines, whose birthday is it again?
没谁的  只是觉着这个派对可能是吸引孩子们
Nobody's. Thought this party might be a good way
在小屋花钱的一种好方式
to get kids to spend money at the shack.
不错
Nice!
这个镇子的年轻人们想要乐趣
The young people of this town want fun,
我就让他们痛快个够
I'll smother 'em with fun!
也许他那些话正是孩子们不来神秘小屋的原因
Maybe comments like that are why kids don't come to the mystery shack.
嘿 嘿  不如你去做点事吧  把这些传单复印了
Hey! Hey! How's about you make yourself useful and copy these flyers?
派对
就在神秘小屋
欢迎小孩和青少年
免费？
哇塞  可以去一趟复印店
Oh, boy! A trip to the copier store!
日历  杯子  T恤  还有些别的
Calendars, mugs, t-shirts and more!
复印店里应有尽有
They got it all at the copier store.
这些不是他们口号  只是我真心这么觉得
That's not their slogan, I just really feel that way about the copier store.
省点事儿吧  你记得我办公室里的那台老复印机么
Save the trouble. You know the old copier in my office?
我最后还是把它给修好了  跟新的一样
I finally fixed the old girl up. Good as new!
蝴蝶啊
Butterflies!
这还能用吗
Does it even work?
搞定了
Success!
后退
Stay back!
噢  我的天啊  梅宝  我觉得这个复印机能复制人类
Oh, my gosh. Mabel, I think this copier can copy human beings!
你知道这意味着什么吗
Do you realize what this means?
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： shortcut
翻译： Sigrid
■
校订： WaitinZ
后期： WaitinZ  liloelva
怪诞小镇  第一季第七集
Gravity Falls  S01E07  Double Dipper
好了  派对的各位
All right, party people,
还有迪普
and Dipper,
我们谈正经的
let's talk business.
苏斯  因为你免费干活儿  并恳求
Soos, because you'll work for free... and you begged...
我让你当DJ
I'm letting you be D.J.
你不会后悔的  派恩斯先生
You won't regret it, Mr. Pines.
我有这本书可以教我把DJ当好好好
I got this book that teached me how to D.J. R-r-r-right.
一点都不振奋人心
Not encouraging.
温蒂  你和梅宝负责售票工作
Wendy, you and Mabel are working the ticket stand.
什么  但斯坦叔公  这个派对是我结交新朋友的绝好机会啊
What?! But Grunkle Stan, this party is my chance to make new friends!
我 我可以和温蒂一起去
I-I could work with Wendy.
要知道如果你去的话
You realize if you do,
你就是答应和温蒂一起一直呆在售票处了
you gotta commit to staying at the ticket stand with Wendy.
不准踏出售票处  只有你俩  独处一整晚
No getting out of it, just the two of you, alone, all night.
我保证
I promise.
啊  干嘛
Aah! What?
呃 呃  我能和你一起在售票台工作  温蒂
Uh, uh, I can work the counter with you, Wendy!
我们亲亲
Let's kiss! Mmm... Mmm...
是 是  你尽管笑
Yeah, yeah, laugh all you want,
但我想了个计划
but I have devised a plan
能让我和温蒂的夜晚美妙无比
to make sure my night with Wendy goes perfect.
计划  噢  你不会要列那些超复杂的清单之类的吧
Plan? Oh, you're not making one of those overcomplicated listy things,
-是吗  -超复杂
- are you? - Overcomplicated?
让我  好吧  等一下啊  好的
Let me just... all right, hold that there... okay...
第一步  以幽默的打趣互相熟悉
"Step one: Getting to know each other with playful banter."
打趣就像是说话  但话语更俏皮点
Banter is like talking, but smarter.
听起来像驴脑袋想的蠢主意
That sounds like a dumb idea for poop-heads.
嗯  你这个  就不是打趣
Yeah, see, this isn't banter.
这种话语正是我和温蒂在一起时要避免的
This is what I want to avoid with Wendy.
最后一步就是邀请她跳舞
The final step is to ask her to dance.
噢  迪普
Oh, Dipper!
我真高兴你来售票处和我一起工作
I'm so happy you decided to work the ticket stand with me!
你做事真有条理  能再让我看看那个清单吗
You're so organized. Show me that checklist again?
如果我遵循这十一步
If I follow steps one through eleven,
就没什么是我绊脚石了
nothing can get in my way.
迪普  你自己才是真正妨碍你的那个人
Dipper you're the one getting in your way.
你为什么就不能直接走过去然后像个正常人一样跟她说话呢
Why can't you just walk up and talk to her like a normal person?
第九步  小妹
Step nine, sister...
像个正常人一样跟她说话
你叔公办的派对不错吧
Can your uncle throw a party or what?
能量  通电了
The energy... it's electric!
呃  灯光  灯光
Uh, lightning. Lightning...
如果有人想走
And if anyone wants to leave,
我就收十五块的离场费
I'm charging an exit fee of 15 bucks!
我只有十三块  我们被困住了
I've only got 13! We're trapped!
第一步  随便的打趣
"Step one: Casual banter."
呃  我有个随便的问题
So, here's a casual question.
你最喜欢什么类型的零食呢
What's your favorite type of snack food?
哦  老兄  这也太难选了
Oh, man. I can't just pick one.
不可能吧  我也是诶
No way! Mine too!
-等等  什么啊  -呃  我是说
-Wait. What? -Uh, I mean...
我的意思是
I mean...
新话题  新话题
New topic! New topic!
动起来  跳起来
Go! Go! Work it! Work it!
哇哦  你身上有个动物诶  我是梅宝
Wow! You've got an animal on your body! I'm Mabel.
嗨  我叫格兰达  这是糖糖
Hi. I'm Grenda. This is Candy.
你为什么把叉子都绑你手指上
Why do you have forks taped to your fingers?
对人体的改良
Improvement of human being.
我找到我的伙伴了
I've found my people.
伙计们  记住  不管是谁 呃
Remember, dudes, whoever, um,
派对甜心们  什么
party hearties... what?...
来赢取派对王冠吧
Get the party crown!
今晚最后得到最多喝彩的人获胜
Most applause at the end of the night wins!
派对王冠  姐要了
Party crown? I'll take that.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
那是谁呀
Who's that?
小镇里最受欢迎的女孩  帕西菲卡・诺斯维斯特
The most popular girl in town: Pacifica Northwest.
在她旁边我总是自我感觉很糟糕
I always feel bad about myself around her.
我不能就这样把王冠给你
I can't just give you the crown.
这怎么说也是个比赛
It's sort of a competition thing.
我不妨说  谁能与我争锋啊
Honestly, who's gonna compete again me?
叉子女  蜥蜴女
Fork girl? Lizard lady?
抱抱我吧  糖糖
Hold me, Candy!
我们在这儿不太受欢迎
Our kind isn't welcome here!
嗨  我要比赛
Hey! I'll compete!
我是梅宝
I'm Mabel.
听起来真像个又胖又老的女人的名字
That sounds like a fat old lady's name.
我就当那是赞美了
I'll take that as a compliment.
那就希望强者得胜吧
May the better partier win.
很高兴认识你
Nice meeting you!
她肯定没戏
She's going down.
哇喔  听起来派对好像很火爆啊
Whoa! Sounds like the party's gettin' nuts!
就让派对王冠之战的战火点燃吧
Let the battle for the party crown begin!
梅宝气势凌人
Mabel comes out strong.
帕西菲卡小心咯
Watch out, pacifica!
我要溜进去  替我掩护一下
I've gotta get in there! Cover for me?
呵呵  呃  那个  我
Heh heh. Um, well, I...
谢了  哥们儿
Thanks, man.
我马上就回来
I'll be back shortly!
我敢肯定如果我只离开一下下的话斯坦不会介意的
I'm sure Stan won't mind if I'm gone for a few minutes.
嗨  你要干嘛  小鬼
Hey! What are you doin', kid?!
这些笨蛋肯定不会自己忽悠自己啊
These suckers aren't going to rip themselves off.
是啊
Yeah!
你保证了的  不记得了
You promised. Remember?
我有吗
I did?
我保证
I promise.
哎  如果我会分身术就好了
Argh. If only I could be two places at once.
注意
危险
我真怀疑这是不是个好注意
I wonder if this is a good idea.
我脑袋真大
I have a really big head.
-那啥  呃  -那啥  呃
-So... uh... -So... uh...
-哈  不好意思  -哈  不好意思
-Ha! Sorry. -Ha! Sorry.
-你先  -你先
-You first. -You first.
-别学我  -别学我
-Stop copying me! -Stop copying me!
啊  嗷 嗷  我的尺骨
Aah! Ow! Ow! Funny bone.
我就叫你  二号
I will call you "number two."
绝对不要
Definitely not.
你知道我一直想有个名字叫
You know a name I've always wanted...
蒂龙  蒂龙
Tyrone. Tyrone.
好的  蒂龙  我们说正经的
Okay, Tyrone, let's get down to business.
我想让你在售票处掩护我
I'm thinkin' you cover me at the ticket stand
然后我去邀请温蒂跳舞
while I ask Wendy to dance.
我很了解计划  哥们儿
I know the plan, buddy.
嘿  我们不会像电影里的克隆人一样
Hey, we're not gonna get jealous and turn on each other
争风吃醋互相残杀吧
like the clones in the movies, are we?
迪普  拜托  你会做出这种事儿来么
Dipper, please. This is you you're talking about.
还有  嘿  你可以随时用水把我分解啊
Plus, hey, you can always just disintegrate me with water.
-对啊  -对啊
-Yeah... -Yeah...
温蒂  好消息
Great news, Wendy.
我找到个人帮我顶班
I got somebody to cover the concessions for me.
太棒了  你可以和我还有罗比一起玩
That's awesome! You can hang out with me and Robbie.
罗比  你记得便利店的迪普吗
Robbie, you remember Dipper from the convenience store.
呃  不记得了
Uh, no.
哟  温蒂  看看我的新吉他
Yo, Wendy, check out my new guitar.
哇  酷
Whoa, cool.
罗比  你真是个愚蠢又自负的骗子
Robbie, you're a stupid, arrogant fraud,
吻我吧  谁叫你会弹吉他呢
but kiss me anyway because you can play guitar.
噢  等一下  我忘了件事
Oh, wait. I forgot something.
我们今晚结婚吧
Let's get married tonight!
嗨  哥们儿  是我  也就是你
Hey, buddy, it's me. You.
我刚有跟你一样的嫉妒幻觉
I just had the same jealousy fantasy.
我如果想和温蒂跳舞的话  我们就得支开罗比
We gotta get rid of Robbie if I ever want to dance with Wendy!
嗨  迪普  我们去沙发那儿坐坐  你打完了去那边找我们
Hey, Dipper! We're gonna go sit on the couch. Meet us when you're done.
噢  不  他们去沙发那儿坐了
Oh, no! They're sitting on the couch!
我们要赶紧想法子
We gotta think of something quick!
-我想到一个  -我也想到了
-I got an idea. -I got the same one.
但我们需要帮忙
But we're gonna need some help.
三号  你就是从那儿出来的
And that's where you come in, number three.
那如果罗比抓到我怎么办  我就孤军奋战了
But what if Robbie catches me? I'll be all alone.
-好吧  再多复制一个吧  -说得也是
-Okay, one more clone. -Makes a good point.
四个迪普  这是“四迪普计划”
Four dippers. This is a four-Dipper plan.
哦噢  卡纸了
Uh-oh, paper jam.
拜托  你不会让我跟他搭档吧
Come on, you're not gonna make me partner up with him, are you?
嘘  别那么无礼
Shh! Don't be rude.
嘿  哥们儿  嘿  没事的
Hey, buddy, hey. It's okay.
好吧  再复制一个
Okay, just one more clone.
是我的永恒
...me is forever
直到永远
Always
永久
Forever
我原来也能那么唱
I used to sing like that...
在我变声之前
Before my voice changed.
帕西菲卡领先
Pacifica pulls ahead!
试试赶超我吧
Try and top that.
噢  格兰达  顺便说一句
Oh, Grenda? By the way,
你真像个摔跤选手  哈哈哈哈
you sound like a professional wrestler. Ha ha ha ha!
我真想把她塞进头套里  然后给她好看
I wanna put her in a headlock and make her feel pain!
姐妹们  不到最后就还有希望
It's not over till it's over, sisters!
看我的
Watch this!
苏斯  给我来
Soos! Give me
你那儿能找到的八十年代最受欢迎的最摇滚歌谣
the eighties's crowd-pleasingest, rock balladiest song you got!
好样的
Excellent.
不要开始不相信
Don't start un-believing
不要不去感觉你的感觉
Never don't not feel your feelings
我要空翻了
Now I'm gonna do a flip!
这是送给你们的
That was for you guys!!!
大伙们  请那辆银红越野自行车的车主
Dudes, would the owner of a silver and red dirt bike
到门口去看看  它正在被人偷走
Please report outside? It is being stolen right now.
等等  什么
Wait... what?!
嘿  给我回来
Hey! Come back here!
噢  难得清静  我想知道那些并非我的家伙是谁
Oh, tough break. I wonder who those guys are
毕竟我现在在这儿呢
that aren't me because I'm right here?
现在我们把音乐放慢片刻
Now we're gonna bring it down for a minute.
女士们  兄弟们  音乐响起
Ladies, dudes, now's the time.
啊  对头  真爱这首歌
Ah, snap! Love this song!
嗨  小傻瓜  现在是你邀请
Hey, goofus! Now's your chance to ask Wendy...
现在是你请温蒂跳舞的机会啊
now's your chance to ask Wendy to dance!
-去啊  快  -我  呃
-Come on! Go! -I... ahh...
啊  我去去就来
Aah! I'll be right back.
嗯  我同意  你不能就这样去跟她跳舞
Oh, I agree. You can't just go and  dance with her.
那舞池简直就是雷区  雷区啊  蒂龙
The dance floor is a mine field! A mine field, Tyrone!
如果音响系统有点小故障怎么样
What if there's a glitch in the sound system!
斯坦会来干涉  罗比也可能回来
Stan might get in the way! Robbie might come back!
变量太多了  我们需要帮忙
There's too many variables! We need help.
好了  迪普们  集合
All right, Dippers, gather round.
时机到了  你们都清楚要怎么做吧
Now's the time. You all clear on what to do?
嘿  苏斯  看呐  一个光点
Hey, Soos, look! A glowing dot!
哦  朋友  我真高兴我转过来看到了
Oh, man, I am so glad I turned my head.
这个点还没让人失望
That dot does not disappoint.
好家伙  搞得像我会上当一样
Right. Like I'm gonna fall for that.
啊  把钱给我  乖乖
Aaah! Gimme that money, Sonny!
暗号来了
There's your cue.
这是邀请温蒂跳舞的绝好时机
It's the perfect moment to ask Wendy to dance.
祝“我”好运
Good luck, me.
我不需要好运  我自有安排
I don't need luck. I have a plan.
-哦  嗨  哥们儿  怎么了  -你 你在这儿干嘛
-Oh, hey, man, what's up? -W-what are you doing here?
我的意思是  你怎么不去舞池呢
I mean, wouldn't you rather be out on the dance floor,
呃  准确说是  在四十二秒内
uh, in, like, exactly 42 seconds?
我只是在等着上洗手间
I'm just waiting for the bathroom.
呃 呃  好吧
Um, um, okay.
呃  闲聊  闲聊  闲聊
Uh, small talk, small talk, small talk...
那么  假如说  这派对上的每个人都被困在了荒岛上
So, hey, let's say everyone at this party gets stuck on a desert island.
你说谁会是带头人
Who do you think the leader would be?
我  呃
I...Uh...
我觉得应该是这个疯子
I think I'd go with this lunatic.
我觉得可能是那边的瘦高个吧
I'd probably go for stretch over there.
呃  也许比较高的人能够到椰子
Uh, because tall people can reach coconuts?
说到高不高  给你看点东东
Speaking of tall, want to see something?
这是我三个兄弟  然后我
Those are my three brothers, and I'm...
噗
Boop!
哈  你是个怪胎
Ha! You were a freak!
是啊
Yep.
你知道吗  在我隐藏我的胎记之前
You know, kids used to make fun of my birthmark
一些孩子总喜欢取笑我
before I started hiding it all the time.
胎记  噢  不  没事
Birthmark? Uh, no, it's nothing!
我我  我说那干嘛
I-I... why did I say that?!
哥们儿  不行  你得给我看看
No way, dude. Now you have to show me.
给我看看嘛  看看
Show me, show me!
北斗七星
The Big Dipper!
这就是你小名的来源吧
That's how you got your nickname!
我还以为是你父母讨厌你还是怎么的呢
I thought your parents just hated you or something.
嗨  我觉得咱俩都是怪胎
Hey, I guess we're both freaks.
-在这儿等我  -当然
-Wait here? -Of course!
嘿
Hey!
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing up here?!
十号已经支开苏斯十五分钟了
Number ten had been distracting Soos for 15 minutes!
-他终究会对那个光点厌烦的  -绝不会
-He's gonna get tired of that dot eventually. -Never!
你们肯定不信  伙计们  我无意中遇到温蒂
You won't believe it, guys. I bumped into Wendy accidentally
并且事情实际上进行得挺顺利
and things are actually going great!
挺好  不过不在计划之中  要我们提醒你吗
That's nice, but not the plan. Do we have to remind you?
哦  天呐  你们真是疯狂
Oh, man, you guys sound crazy.
听着  也许我们不需要计划了  懂吗
Look, maybe we don't need the plan anymore, ya know?
也许我可以很正常地走过去跟她说话
Maybe I could just go talk to her like a normal person.
你闭上你的嘴
You bite your tongue!
如果你不按计划来
If you're not gonna stick to the plan,
那你就不应该是和温蒂跳舞的那个迪普
maybe you shouldn't be the Dipper to dance with Wendy.
如果你考虑一下
If you think about it...
朋友们  别啊  我们说过我们互相不翻脸的啊
Guys, come on. We said we weren't gonna turn on each other.
我想我们都知道我们是在撒谎
I think we all knew we were lying.
别 别  喂
No! No! Hey!
别啊  等等
No, wait!
-啊  我在这儿不能呼吸了  -你可以的
-Aaah! I can't breathe in here! -Yeah, you can!
另外那儿有给你的零食和一本彩画本
Plus there's snacks and a coloring book in there for you!
好嘞  现在那个原始迪普  或者“经典迪普”
Okay, so now that original Dipper... or "Dipper Classic"...
再也不在了  我提名我自己去和温蒂跳舞
is no longer fit for it, I nominate myself to dance with Wendy instead.
我在这儿的时间最久  所以应该是我
I've been around the longest, so it should be me.
大家说对吧  我是说  按逻辑  逻辑来说
Right? I mean, logically. Logically, guys.
说得好  说得好
Fair point, fair point.
可是  或许应该是我和温蒂跳舞呢
Counterpoint, maybe I should get to dance with Wendy
因为我来这儿的时间最短啊
because I've been around for the least.
你说的真是毫无道理
That makes, like, zero sense.
你才毫无道理呢
You make zero sense!
-注意点啊  -别推人啊你
-Watch it! -Don't shove people!
嗨  要来点芝士和饼干么  哥们儿
Hey, you want some cheese and crackers, buddy?
哎哟
Yikes.
嘿  兄弟们
Hey, guys?
如果你们被关在小屋子里会怎么做
What would you do if you were trapped in a closet?
逃啊
Break out.
温
Wend...
伙计  你还是省省吧  你被降服了
Come on, man, give it up. You're overpowered.
等一等  兄弟们  想想啊
Hold on, guys, think about it.
我们的思想和身体都是完全一致的
We're exact equals mentally and physically.
如果我们开打  就会没完没了啊
If we start fighting, it'll just go on for infinity!
也对哦  我们还是算了吧
That's true. Maybe we should just give up...
复制人大战
Clone fight!!!
别打自己了  别打自己了
Quit hitting myself! Quit hitting myself!
亲  住手啊  是我啊
Guys, come on, it's me!
嘿  你  滚开
Hey, you! Get  off!
嘿  经典迪普在逃跑
Hey! Classic Dipper's getting away!
不  朋友们
No, friends.
是我  七号
It's me. Number seven.
那不是我  伙计们  不是我
That's not me, guys, that's not me!
抓住他
Get him!
退后  退后
Stay back, stay back...
噗  完蛋了  完蛋了
Boo! Lame. Lame.
对卡纸迪普来说
还是这样比较好
哼  这滋味不好受吧
Huh. How 'bout that?
-你  -噢哦
-You! -Uh-oh.
最后一曲  伙计们  然后就到
One more song, dudes, and then it's time
派对王冠的颁奖时间了
for the bestowing of the party crown!
到时候将会
It's gonna be the...
搞定
Nailed it.
帕西菲卡  我想说的是不管谁赢
Pacifica, I just want to say that whoever wins,
这都是个超赞的派对
it's been a super-fun party.
哦  有人好像觉得她要赢似的
Aww. It thinks it's gonna win.
嗨  你听到没
Hey, did you hear that?
人们为那群奇葩女鼓掌呢
People clapping for the weird girls?
是哦  我也没听到
Yeah. Me neither.
说  说我可以和温蒂跳舞
Say it! Say I can dance with Wendy!
妄想
Never!
-温蒂  -温蒂
-Wendy? -Wendy?
罗比
Robbie!
别说了
Shut up.
-哎  我们搞砸了  -哎  我们搞砸了
-Ohh. We blew it, man. -Ohh. We blew it, man.
我也不知道  你想来点苏打水或者别的什么么
I don't know. You wanna go grab a couple sodas or something?
派对王冠投票开始
Let the party crown voting commence!
梅宝  祝你好运
Good luck, Mabel.
投梅宝的请鼓掌
Applaud to vote for Mabel!
耶  梅宝加油
Yeah! Go, Mabel!
我们来看看故障测量仪
Let's check the applause-o-meter.
噢 噢  相当不错哦
Oh... Oh... Pretty good...
接下来是另一位选手  帕西菲卡
And your next contestant,  pacifica!
哦噢  平局
Uh-oh! A tie!
这  貌似  从来没发生过啊
This has, like, never happened before.
女士们先生们  我们的  冠军诞生了
Ladies and gentlemen, we... we have a winner.
比赛的冠军是帕西菲卡・诺斯维斯特
The winner of the contest is Pacifica Northwest.
谢谢你  乔治
Thank you, Jorge.
谢谢在场的每一位
Thank you, everyone!
欢迎大家来我父母的船上参加余兴派对
Everyone come to the after-party at my parents' boat!
帕西菲卡  帕西菲卡  帕西菲卡
Pacifica! Pacifica! Pacifica...
哦  对不起  让你们失望了
Ohh. Sorry I let you guys down.
如果你们想走  我能理解
I understand if you want to leave.
那样的话我们就会错过借宿了
But then we would miss the sleep-over.
-什么东西  -我们想打电话给妈妈
-The what? -We want to call our moms
然后在这和你一起过夜
and sleep over here with you!
你完全是个摇滚巨星
You're like a total rock star!
我还有帅哥杂志
I have magazine boys.
真的吗  你们真好
Really? You guys!
也许我们没有帕西菲卡那么多的朋友
Maybe we don't have as many friends as pacifica,
但我们有彼此  这样我就觉得很知足了
but we have each other, and that is pretty good, I think.
苏斯  再放一首歌
Soos! Play another song!
我们要嗨一整晚
This thing's going all night!
早就想到了  我的小明星
Way ahead of you, hambone.
不如人愿的夜晚啊
Some night, huh?
唉  你觉得我们真配得上跟温蒂跳舞么
Ahh. You think we really even have a chance with Wendy?
我是说  她十五岁  我们才十二
I mean, she's 15, we're 12.
哥们儿  我也不知道啊  但愿可以吧
I don't know, man. I hope so.
但我们现在这样毫无进展啊
But we're making zero progress the way we're doing it.
你和她唯一一次不错的谈话
The only good conversation you had with her
就是你没有按清单出牌的那次
was when you didn't do any of that list stuff.
我知道  梅宝说得对  我确实成了自己的障碍
I know. Mabel was right, I do get in my own way.
-简直啊  -简直啊
-Literally! -Literally!
噢  完了  别看我
Oh, boy, don't look now.
-蒂龙  -没事的  好哥们儿  我来这一趟挺好的
-Tyrone! -It's okay, dude, I had a good run.
记得我们说过的
Remember what we talked about.
嗯  当然
Uh, of course!
嘿  答应我在温蒂面前再别那么软弱了  好吗
Hey, and quit being such a wimp around Wendy, okay?
看在我的面子上
For my sake!!!!
蒂龙
Tyrone!
你是我唯一的知音啊
You were the only one who understood.
迪普  你去哪儿了
Dipper! Where have you been?
快来见见我的女朋友们
Meet my girlfriends!
找着了
Found it.